<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>DevOps on Adam Dingman - Cloud, DevOps, IoT</title><link>https://adamdingman.net/categories/devops/</link><description>Recent content in DevOps on Adam Dingman - Cloud, DevOps, IoT</description><image><url>https://adamdingman.net/images/profile-photo.jpg</url><link>https://adamdingman.net/images/profile-photo.jpg</link></image><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 00:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://adamdingman.net/categories/devops/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Case for Pull Request Build Validation</title><link>https://adamdingman.net/posts/build-validation/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://adamdingman.net/posts/build-validation/</guid><description>What is the problem to be solved? The Continuous Integration (CI) process is failing after following the approval of a pull request (PR) and the subsequent merge of code.
Not only does this block this specific change set from flowing through the CI/CD process, but it can also block all others as the breaking change was already merged into the branch that is used to trigger the CI process.
Example After a pull request is approved and the feature branch is merged, the CI process is triggered to build and test the code.</description></item><item><title>Deploy an AWS Budget using Pulumi</title><link>https://adamdingman.net/posts/pulumi-aws-budgets/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://adamdingman.net/posts/pulumi-aws-budgets/</guid><description>What is Pulumi? Pulumi is yet another Infrastructure as Code (IaC) tool for deploying infrastructure using declaritive language which offers you the ability to pick your language of choice amongst TypeScript, JavaScript, Python, Go, .NET, Java, and YAML to define your infrastructure.
How am I using Pulumi? I really wanted a quick and easy means to get a feel for the basic structure of a Pulumi project and to get a feel for the CLI.</description></item></channel></rss>